Okay, so the design of our class Movie, is
好的 我们类 Movie 的设计
here on the top right, [SOUND] and I'm going
位于右上角 [声音]我将从
to begin, with a blank programming file. I have
一个空白的编程文件开始 我
named it, media.py, and it is saved inside a
将它命名为 media.py 然后
folder called, movies. Now, to write a new class,
保存在文件夹 movies 内 现在 要编写一个新类
[SOUND] I will used the Python keyword, class. And
[声音]我将使用 Python 关键字 class 然后
I will name it, Movie. You've probably notices, that
我将它命名为 Movie 你可能会注意到 这个名字
the first letter of the name of the class M,
的首字母是一个
is in uppercase. Now, this letter doesn't necessarily
大写的 M 这个字母不一定必须是
need to be in uppercase, but, the Google style
大写的 但是 Google 的
guide for Python suggests that it should be.
《Python 风格指南》建议用大写
Now, what is this thing called the Google style
你可能会问 Google 的
guide for Python you ask, Well, let's Google
《Python 风格指南》是个什么东西 不如我们来 Google
it. The first link here looks good to me.
一下吧 第一个链接就可以
Now, this Style Guide, provides conventions to programmers all
这个风格指南提供了全世界
over the world. On how to write their programs.
程序员用于编写程序的惯例
If you scroll down a bit You will notice
如果你往下滚动鼠标 你会发现
that there are conventions on everything, from how to name
它涵盖方方面面的惯例 包括如何命名
things, to how to write comments. By the way,
如何写注释 顺便说一句
the link to this webpage, is available in the instructor
讲师笔记中也提供了这个
notes. I recommend that you read through this document.
链接 我建议你通读一遍这个文档
If you click on this link called Naming, you will
如果你点击这个名为“命名”的链接 你
notice that, when defining a class name, Google recommends that
会发现 在定义类名称时 Google 建议
the first letter of that name be in capital letters.
名称的首字母为大写
Okay, back to the code. Now, thus far, we've
好的 回到代码 目前为止
encountered one new key word, called class. In fact, we
我们遇到了一个新的关键字 称为“类” 事实上
are going to come across several new words in this
我们将在课程中遇到好几个新词
lesson, and I want to list them all, in one
我想在一个地方把它列出来
place for handy reference. The word class, is the first
便于大家参考 “类”就是
one on that list. We will review, all the words
这个列表中的第一个词 在这门课程的末尾
on this list before we end this lesson. So, you
我们将回顾列表中的所有词 你
may have noticed that our class, is empty thus far.
可能注意到 到目前为止我们的类依然是空的
Now, to figure out what I want to do next
要弄清楚接下来做什么 我得
with it, I will go back to my design. So,
返回我的设计 好的
here I am, back with my class design. Now, I
现在我回到了课程设计 我知道了
know that eventually, I would want to create multiple instances
最终我要创建类 movie 的
of the class movie. Instances like, Toy Story and
多个实例 如 Toy Story 和
Avatar. I also know that I have previously created instances
Avatar 我也知道我之前创建了
of class Turtle. Instances like Brad, and to do that,
类 Turtle 的实例 如 Brad 为此我
I had to write a piece of code that read,
编写了这样一条代码：
turtle.Turtle, so I guess I will have to write a piece of code like
turtle.Turtle 我想我得编写类似的
this, to create Toy Story, an instance of class Movie. Let's do that next.
代码来创建类 Movie 的实例 Toy Story 这就是我们下一步要做的